<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<act_A>
		<number_1>
			<context_1>You are the leader of the biggest underground resistance army. How did you come to this position? Assassination, bribery, stealing and many other organized crimes.\n</context_1>
			<context_2>Now that you are powerful enough, you start thinking about a revolution. So, you start planning and it all culminates now, with the meeting of all the higher-ups in your underground organization.\n\n</context_2>
			<dialog_1>(voices in the crowd): Silence! The leader is approaching!\n(All people stop speaking and they all start looking at the door. They were right, the leader was coming.)\n</dialog_1>
			<dialog_2>General: Dear Leader, I am glad you are here. We need to sort out the plans for the revolution. We have been talking here for hours and we can't get to decide on one. You need to decide.\nRightHandMan: I have placed the plans folder on the desk in your office. If you didn't have the time to read them, we will recap them for you.</dialog_2>
			<decision_1> (1)> You were to slow on giving me those papers. I want you to tell me the plan that I presented last meeting.</decision_1>
			<decision_2> (2)> I glanced over the details of my plan but didn't have time for anything else. General, please tell me your plan.</decision_2>
			<decision_3> (3)> My plan is brilliant, and the General's is intelligent. Right Hand Man, what do you have to say?</decision_3>
			<decision_4> (4)> Of course I read them all. I have finally come here to decide the course of action!</decision_4>
		</number_1>
		<number_2>
			<dialog_1>(Markus, leader of liberal party in exile):We heard your plan the other day and we wrote it up. It is a good idea to talk with the prime minister. He is sympathetic with us. He may help us in the revolution! </dialog_1>
			<decision_2> (2)> Now that I know everything about my plan, I wish to talk with the General about his plan.</decision_2>
			<decision_3> (3)> My plan is brilliant. Right Hand Man, can you remind me what your plan was?</decision_3>
			<decision_4> (4)> Now that I know the details of my plan, I will make the final decision!</decision_4>
		</number_2>
		<number_3>
			<dialog_1> (General) - Your plan is glorious, but I don't think the prime minister will cooperate, due to his friendship with the emperor. We shall need to organize our militia and take power by popular force!
			</dialog_1>
			<decision_3> (3)> My plan is brilliant, and the General's is intelligent. Right Hand Man, what do you have to say?</decision_3>
			<decision_4> (4)> Of course, we need a backup plan. I don't care about the Right Hand Man's plan. I will make my final decision!</decision_4>
		</number_3>
		<number_4>
		    <dialog_1> (Right Hand Man) - We don't have a plan for diplomacy, we need force, fast force. Decisive force. We need to immediately destroy the empire!
			</dialog_1>
			<decision_4> (4)> Of course, like you say.... . They are all okay plans. I will now make my final decision!</decision_4>
		</number_4>
		<number_5>
		    <dialog_1>(You) - I have decided on the final plan. The best. The greatest. It shall be</dialog_1>
			<decision_1> (1)> MY PLAN!</decision_1>
			<decision_2> (2)> THE GENERAL'S PLAN!</decision_2>
			<decision_3> (3)> THE RIGHT HAND MAN'S PLAN!</decision_3>
	</number_5>
	</act_A>
	<act_B1>
		<number_1>
			<dialog_1>(General) - We need to make a decision. What should we do? I mean, neither I nor you had a perfect plan. We need to check the details. </dialog_1>
			<dialog_2>(Soldier) - Dear Leader! General! Bad news! Word that the current prime minister is... dead!</dialog_2>
			<dialog_3>(General) - Well, this is inconvenient. Boss, how we shall proceed?</dialog_3>
			<decision_1> (1)> This is a problem, but we are able to overcome this. General, please continue with your plan!</decision_1>
			<decision_2> (2)> Our reasoning was wrong. We need to talk with the Right Hand Man, he was in the right!</decision_2>
		</number_1>
		<number_2>
			<dialog_1>(General) - Boss, now that we have decided on the plans, we need to take the next course of action.</dialog_1>
			<decision_1> (1)> It will be best to recruit more militia.</decision_1>
			<decision_2> (2)> Right Hand Man has been very suspicious lately. We need to get him assassinated. Recruit later!</decision_2>
		</number_2>
		<number_3>
			<dialog_1>(Phone - Assassin) - We have the Right Hand Man cornered, shall we continue?</dialog_1>
			<dialog_2>(You) - Yes, do what is necessary!</dialog_2>
			<dialog_3>(Phone) - Aaaaa! aaaa! Ahahaha! Ah... Aaaaa!</dialog_3>
			<decision_1>(Phone - Assassin) - He is dead!</decision_1>
			<decision_2>(Phone - Right Hand Man) - You can't kill me! I'm GOD, DESTROYER OF WORLDS!</decision_2>
		</number_3>
		<number_4>
			<dialog_1>(General) - Sir, but from where shall we recruit? The rural areas are a safe bet. In the cities, our fate is... debatable.</dialog_1>
			<decision_1> (1)> From the villages!</decision_1>
			<decision_2> (2)> From the cities!</decision_2>
			<after_1>The recruitment went fine! We have the upper hand and we will surely beat the poorly trained imperial militia.
			</after_1>
			<after_2>The recruitment failed! We accidentally exposed our plans to the imperial agents! Abort everything! We are going to Argentina!
			</after_2>
			<after_3>We were also contacted by some old veterans that aren't happy with the current regime. They will make great assets in our plan. 
			</after_3>
		</number_4>
		<number_5>
			<dialog_1>(General) - Now that we have made all the necessary preparations, we are ready to act. Sir, what shall we do next?
			</dialog_1>
			<decision_1> (1) > We need to do the population’s bidding. We shall organize a great strike!
			</decision_1>
			<decision_2> (2) > Popular revolution is what we shall do. We will overcome this difficult period in our people's lives!
			</decision_2>
			<decision_3> (3) > We need to restore greatness in our people!
			</decision_3>
		</number_5>
	</act_B1>
	<act_B2>
	</act_B2>
</text>
